A Guide to the Policy Office: General Assembly Legislation of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1993.
Library of Virginia
- General Assembly Legislation, 1991.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1991.
    - HB 1455 (91) Non-resident insurance agent licenses, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HB 1456 (91) Cellular mobile radio communications carrier, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HB 1458 (91) Judicial Council, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HB 1459 (91) Copies of originals as evidence, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HB 1460 (91) Loaded firearms in of city of 200,000 population or more, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HB 1461 (91) Dept. of Correctional Education, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HB 1464 (91) Claims in public oyster grounds, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HB 1468 (91) Disability certification for elderly and handicapped - Personal property tax exemptions, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HB 1470 (91) Patient and community health education programs, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HB 1471 (91) Grants for worksite health promotion programs, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HB 1473 (91) Virginia Medicaid Drug Formulary, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HB 1475 (91) Infertility treatment, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HB 1477 (91) Students - Tuition relief, refund and reinstatement, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HB 1480 (91) Temporary restrictions - City charters, annexation and immunity, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HB 1485 (91) Warrant or summons - Notification of issuance, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 1)
    - HB 1486 (91) Arrest process, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 1)
    - HB 1488 (91) Local school boards, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 1)
    - HB 1491 (91) Conveyance by husband and wife, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 1)
    - HB 1492 (91) Local license tax, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 1)
    - HB 1497 (91) Local court appointed special advocate programs, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 1)
    - HB 1499 (91) Virging Retirement System and State Policy Officer's Retirement System, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 1)
    - HB 1500 (91) Dept. of Motor Vehicles - Electronic filings, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1501 (91) Assessments for local improvements, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1502 (91) Local dates for filing returns, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1503 (91) Civil actions, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1504 (91) Virginia Housing Partnership Revolving Fund, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1505 (91) Uniform Statewide Building Code, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1506 (91) Electric and natural gas submeterings, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1513 (91) Alternative forms of security, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1514 (91) Depositions, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - HB 1519 (91) Official insect of the Commonwealth, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 3)
    - HB 1520 (91) Classification of tangible personal property, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 3)
    - HB 1521 (91) Tax credits for substance abuse advertising, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 3)
    - HB 1525 (91) Motor vehicles, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 3)
    - HB 1529 (91) Parole eligibility, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 3)
    - HB 1532 (91) Will - Filing suit to impeach or establish, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 3)
    - HB 1535 (91) Dept. of Transportation - easements, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 3)
    - HB 1539 (91) Unlawful wearing of an officer's uniform, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - HB 1541 (91) Motor vehicle dealer advertising, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - HB 1542 (91) Motor vehicle dealer advertising, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - HB 1543 (91) Motor vehicle hood scoops, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - HB 1545 (91) Subdivision ordinance, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - HB 1549 (91) Coal Surface Mining Reclamation Fund, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - HB 1550 (91) Driving without a valid license, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - HB 1551 (91) Health Dept. employees - Salare supplements, 1991. (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - HB 1553 (91) State license tax on alcoholic beverages, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HB 1554 (91) Alcoholic Beverage Control - Bed and breakfast establishments, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HB 1557 (91) Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HB 1558 (91) Acquittal by reason of insanity, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HB 1563 (91) Real Estate Board, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HB 1564 (91) Judicial authorization for treatment, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HB 1565 (91) State Networking Users Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HB 1566 (91) Juvenile intake, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HB 1568 (91) School boards - Overdue book fees, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HB 1569 (91) Southwest Virginia Higher Education Center, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HB 1572 (91) Treasury Board, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HB 1574 (91) Possession of a firearm on school property, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HB 1575 (91) Environmental reviews of highway / road contruction projects, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HB 1577 (91) State Board of Health, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HB 1578 (91) Jail workforces, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HB 1579 (91) Home / electronic incarceration program, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HB 1581 (91) Condominium Act, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1582 (91) Dedicated funds, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1583 (91) Employees - Payment of wages, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1584 (91) Patient injuries by nursing homes, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1586 (91) Optometry, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1588 (91) Beer and wine importers, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1589 (91) Banks issuing certificates of deposit, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1590 (91) Wet Settlement Act, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1592 (91) Bail, bond and recognizance, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1595 (91) Nursing home education programs - Public school divisions, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1596 (91) License tax on savings and loan associations, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1597 (91) Summons for debt or interogatories upon a corporate debtor, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1599 (91) Coal and Gas Road Improvement Advisory Committee, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - HB 1602 (91) Secretary of Education and Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1604 (91) Pay per call services, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1605 (91) Boat registration and titling fees, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1607 (91) Motorcycle headlights, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1611 (91) Former officers and employees of counties - Restriction on activities, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1614 (91) Ambulance Authority for the City of Richmond, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1615 (91) Natural Death Act, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1616 (91) Administration of estates, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1617 (91) Construction of a power to invade, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1618 (91) Reckless driving, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1619 (91) Virginia byway - Ball's Neck, Northumberland County, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1620 (91) Southeast Interstate Low-level Radioactive Waste Managem, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - HB 1622 (91) Member or director agreements, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - HB 1624 (91) Retrieval of dogs by hunters, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - HB 1625 (91) Family life education materials, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - HB 1632 (91) Securities Act, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - HB 1633 (91) Manufactured housing, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - HB 1639 (91) Joint exercise of powers by local governments, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - HB 1662 (91) Tangible personal property - Valuation, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1665 (91) Adoption of zoning ordinances, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1669 (91) Bingo games, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1670 (91) Legal defense for police officers, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1671 (91) Fire insurance policies, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1672 (91) Motor vehicle insurance policies, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1673 (91) Code provisions in ordinances, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1674 (91) Agricultural operations deemed nuisances, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1675 (91) Animal health regulations, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1676 (91) Motor vehicle windshields - Signs, decals, stickers, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1677 (91) Equitable distribution, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1678 (91) Retirement benefits, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - HB 1682 (91) Influencing decisions of financial institutions, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1684 (91) Cable television service - Tampering with or unlawful us, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1691 (91) Unlawful detainer actions, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1693 (91) Annulments, affirmance and divorce, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1696 (91) School dropout prevention, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1697 (91) Limited partnerships, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1698 (91) Filing tax returns and paying taxes - Extensions, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1701 (91) New Kent County Game Refuge, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1702 (91) Special service districts in consolidated cities, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 1705 (91) Agricultural Commodity boards, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - HB 1707 (91) Reports of parent's social security number at time of child's birth, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - HB 1708 (91) Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries - Real estate in King and Queen County, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - HB 1711 (91) Unemployment compensation benefits - Disqualification, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - HB 1713 (91) Classification of tangible personal property, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - HB 1715 (91) Superintendent of State Police, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - HB 1717 (91) Virginia Athletic Board, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - HB 1722 (91) Property title records of limited partnerships, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - HB 1724 (91) Demolition of historic structures, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1727 (91) Durable power of attorney, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1728 (91) Bad check cases - Admissible evidence, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1729 (91) Legitimacy of children conceived by reproductive technology, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1730 (91) Workers' compensation - Disallowed, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1731 (91) Door to door vendors - Executive form of government, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1734 (91) Taxation - Assessment, credit, filing, withholding, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1736 (91) Tuition - Out of state students, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1737 (91) Subdivision ordinances, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1738 (91) Construction contracts - Stipulated indemnification provisions, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - HB 1740 (91) Custody, visitation and support, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1741 (91) Limited partnerships or corporations - Fictitious and assumed names, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1742 (91) Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1744 (91) Child support enforcement, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1748 (91) Vocational education projects - Sale of, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1749 (91) Private security services businesses, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1750 (91) State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1751 (91) Property exemptions, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1753 (91) Firearms - Use or display in committing a felony, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HB 1755 (91) Partnership certificate, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1756 (91) Placement for adoption, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1759 (91) Judgment rate of interest, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1762 (91) Limited partnership - Changing registered agent, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1763 (91) Horse racing - Pari-mutuel wagering, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1764 (91) Hotel Roanoke Conference Center Commission Act, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1767 (91) Design-Build and construction management contracts, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1768 (91) Special elections, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1769 (91) Dates for filing tax returns - Counties, cities, towns, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - HB 1771 (91) Collection of fines, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 1772 (91) Clerks of court - General receivers, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 1773 (91) Clerks - Indexing, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 1774 (91) Grand jurors - Selection and qualification, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 1776 (91) Auctioneers, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 1778 (91) Commission on Early Childhood and Child Day Care Programs, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 1786 (91) Electrical transmission lines, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 1788 (91) Jail boards and authorities - Location of jails or jail farms, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 1790 (91) Deed of trust - Proper form of recordation, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1791 (91) Surviving spouse intestate share, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1794 (91) Child labor laws, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1797 (91) Structured settlements for minors, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1798 (91) Medicare supplement policies, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1799 (91) Motor vehicle warranty adjustment programs, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1800 (91) Installment sales obligations - Acceleration clauses, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1805 (91) Bail bonds - Drug testing, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1806 (91) Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1808 (91) Representation in administrative proceedings, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - HB 1811 (91) Juvenile detention facilities - Private operation, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1813 (91) Workers' compensation, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1818 (91) Involuntary admission and mental health treatment, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1823 (91) Virging Retirement System death benefits, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1825 (91) Court of Appeals, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1830 (91) Interest rates, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1831 (91) Virginia - West Virginia boundary, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1832 (91) Tagging or locking hazardous energy sources (OSHA), 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1835 (91) Government Non-Arbitrage Investment Act, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1843 (91) Labor Unions - Registration, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - HB 1844 (91) Expedited land development review, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - HB 1846 (91) Limited liability companies, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - HB 1848 (91) Virginia Port Authority, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - HB 1850 (91) Trailer and semi-trailers - Safety inspections, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - HB 1852 (91) Gasoline - Cash-sale price, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - HB 1855 (91) Financial institutions - Mergers, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - HB 1857 (91) State Treasurer - Securities and stock, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1859 (91) Pre-sentence investigations, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1862 (91) Family day-care homes - Voluntary register, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1872 (91) Board of zoning appeals, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1873 (91) State Board of Health and Dept. of Health, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1875 (91) Virginia Savings Bank Act, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1876 (91) Credit union authorized investments, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1877 (91) Life insurance proceeds - Interest, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1878 (91) Credit Union, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1879 (91) Driving after license revocation or suspension, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HB 1883 (91) Hunting - Charles City County, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - HB 1886 (91) Concealed weapons, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - HB 1889 (91) Workers' Compensation, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - HB 1891 (91) Minimum wages, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - HB 1896 (91) Lapse of insurance policy, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - HB 1901 (91) Application of the Rule of 78, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - HB 1902 (91) Authority of the Governor to suspend state mandates on local governments, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - HB 1906 (91) Burial life insurance, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - HB 1911 (91) Collection out of estate, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - HB 1912 (91) Prisoner medical records, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - HB 1913 (91) Automobile Parking Authority - Town of Vienna, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - HB 1915 (91) Criminal history information checks - Transfer of weapons, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - HB 1917 (91) Motor vehicles - Interior lights, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - HB 1920 (91) Pesticide Control Board, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1921 (91) Administrative Support Orders - Withholding of earnings, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1923 (91) Enjoining environmental and health hazards, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1925 (91) Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1927 (91) James Madison University - Board of Visitors, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1929 (91) Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1930 (91) Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1931 (91) Virginia Housing Development Authority - Taxable housing bonds, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1932 (91) Wrongful death, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HB 1935 (91) Institutions of Higher Education - Retirement, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HB 1939 (91) Virginia Transportation Contract Revenue Bonds, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HB 1944 (91) Standards of quality, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HB 1949 (91) Chesapeake CHAMPS program - Dispersing controlled substances, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HB 1951 (91) Distribution of estates, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HB 1957 (91) Indecent liberties with children, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HB 1959 (91) State Veterinarian, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HB 1960 (91) Animal warden training courses, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HB 1963 (91) Medical care facilities - Certificate of public need, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - HB 1964 (91) Driving while intoxicated, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - HB 1966 (91) Criminal Justice Services Board, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - HB 1968 (91) Zoning ordinances - Affordable housing, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - HB 1970 (91) Sporting events and competitions, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - HB 1973 (91) Status of children of assisted conception, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - HB 1975 (91) Support of spouse and children, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - HB 1979 (91) Insurance Guarantee Association, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - HB 1980 (91) Virginia Indoor Clean Air Act, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - HB 1981 (91) Costs of solid waste management, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - HB 1982 (91) Medical malpractice, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - HB 1983 (91) Boat operators, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - HB 1984 (91) Divorce - Equitable distribution, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - HB 1987 (91) Dept. of World Trade, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - HB 1990 (91) Assault and battery of family, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - HB 1992 (91) Placement for adoption by a parent or guardian, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - HB 1995 (91) Special education programs, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - HB 1996 (91) Home instruction for children, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - HB 2001 (91) Absentee ballots - Military and overseas voters, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - HB 2002 (91) Compromises of claims, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - HB 2004 (91) Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2009 (91) Local parking regulation, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2011 (91) Limousines and executive sedans, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2012 (91) Certificates of self insurance, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2013 (91) State Board of Social Services, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2016 (91) Finance charges to open accounts, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2019 (91) Classification of tangible personal property, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2021 (91) Sturgeon research permits, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2022 (91) Virginia Marine Patrol, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2023 (91) Weights and Measures, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2025 (91) School boards - Disciplinary authority, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - HB 2026 (91) Workers' Compensation Act, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - HB 2029 (91) Transportation district commissioners, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - HB 2032 (91) Planning district commissioners, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - HB 2034 (91) Judicial vacancies, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bills, 1991.
    - SB 59 (91) Penalties for felonies, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - SB 178 (91) Industrial Development and Revenue Bond Act, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - SB 316 (91) Fair Elections Practices Act, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - SB 376 (91) School employee arrests, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - SB 386 (91) Commissioner of Accounts - Fiduciaries, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - SB 389 (91) Divorce - Domicile, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - SB 400 (91) Local taxes - Assessment and refund, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - SB 428 (91) Baloon relsease, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - SB 505 (91) Exemption from property tax - ARC of Northern Virginia, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - SB 508 (91) Conservators of the Peace, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - SB 509 (91) Hirst/Brault Expressway and Orange Springs Bridge designation, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - SB 512 (91) Flashing amber warning lights, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - SB 513 (91) Volunteer fire and rescue - Driving records, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - SB 514 (91) Special county policemen - Bonds, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - SB 515 (91) Commissioner of the Revenue, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - SB 522 (91) Charter - City of Galax, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - SB 528 (91) Charter - City of Roanoke, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - SB 529 (91) Charter - City of Roanoke, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - SB 537 (91) Demolition of historic buildings, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - SB 545 (91) Charter - Town of Pocahontas, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - SB 547 (91) Foster care plans and review, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - SB 548 (91) Immunizations, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - SB 549 (91) Dump stations, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - SB 552 (91) Institutions of Higher Education - Capital projects, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - SB 554 (91) Virginia Life, Accident and Sickness Insurance Guarantee Association, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - SB 555 (91) Medical scholarships conditions, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 558 (91) State-owned bottomlands, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 559 (91) Pay-per-call services, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 560 (91) Deferred compensation plans, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 561 (91) Line of Duty Act - Free tuition, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 562 (91) Electrical transmission lines, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 567 (91) General District Courts - Jurisdiction, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 568 (91) Sexual abuse - Reporting, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 569 (91) Accepting children for placement, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SB 572 (91) Virginia Health Spa Act, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - SB 574 (91) Regional jail and jail farm boards, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - SB 575 (91) Licenses - Suspension or revocation, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - SB 576 (91) Foreign corporations, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - SB 577 (91) Involuntary termination of corporate existence, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)